{
    "subject": "Ferdinand_VII_of_Spain",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Maria_Christina_of_the_Two_Sicilies",
    "human_readable": "Ferdinand VII of Spain is married to Maria Christina of the Two Sicilies.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9620879888534546,
            "question": "Is Maria Christina of the Two Sicilies related to Ferdinand VII?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9498195648193359,
            "question": "Was Ferdinand VII of Spain married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9496667981147766,
            "question": "Who was Ferdinand VII of Spain married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9337068200111389,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Ferdinand VII and Maria Christina of the Two Sicilies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.906524121761322,
            "question": "To whom was Ferdinand VII of Spain wed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8363663554191589,
            "question": "Who is Maria Christina of the Two Sicilies?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7691749334335327,
            "question": "What is the connection between Ferdinand VII and Maria Christina?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7201203107833862,
            "question": "What was the name of Ferdinand VII's wife?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7153167128562927,
            "question": "Were Ferdinand VII and Maria Christina from the same country?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6429015398025513,
            "question": "Can you tell me about the marriage of Ferdinand VII?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Ferdinand VII of Spain is married to Maria Christina of the Two Sicilies.",
            "html": "yago_28415_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were Ferdinand VII and Maria Christina from the same country?",
            "html": "yago_28415_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What was the name of Ferdinand VII's wife?",
            "html": "yago_28415_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the connection between Ferdinand VII and Maria Christina?",
            "html": "yago_28415_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28415_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28415_111.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28415_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28415_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28415_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28415_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28415_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28415_53.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28415_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28415_75.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "After analyzing the provided context information, I can conclude that:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about Maria Cristina of the Two Sicilies being married to King Ferdinand VII of Spain. In fact, there are multiple mentions of their marriage in different files (e.g., file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/yago_28415/re-ranker-msmarco/34.txt and others), which confirm the correctness of this triple."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information supporting that King Ferdinand VII of Spain was indeed married to Maria Christina of the Two Sicilies. For instance, `3.txt` states, \"Maria Christina of the Two Sicilies (27 April 1806 \u2013 22 August 1878) was Queen consort of Spain from 1829 to 1833 and Regent of Spain from 1833 to 1840 through her marriage to Ferdinand VII.\" This clearly indicates their marital relationship."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}